(Leonard:)...if I wasn't in shock
that Sheldon has girl problems.
Well, Leonard, go ahead and mock.
It's like my daddy always said:
"Shelly, women aren't anything
but flipping pains in the bottom."
(Leonard:)That's what your father used to say?
(Sheldon:)Well, I took out the bad words
and the "yeehaw," but you get the gist.
If you don't wanna go to the party,
just don't go. You're a grown man.
Act like one. Tell Amy you wanna spend
the weekend having a sleepover...
(Howard:)...and playing video games
with your friends.
Yeah, maybe she'll dig it.
Women like a firm hand on the tiller.
l can never find the tiller.
l got a book. It didn't help.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I always thought
if I were ever enslaved...
(Sheldon:)...it would be by an advanced species
from another planet...
(Sheldon:)...not some hotsy-totsy from Glendale.
l downloaded an app
that might be helpful in this situation.